Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
And today...
Now that my arms are better, I gotta work real hard and make up for lost time!
It looks like peace has finally returned to the Black Bull's hideout.
Kinda boring with nothing going on around here, don't you think?
I could get used to this.
Then, a lone mage stepped in and spoiled the tranquility.
Listen up!
He was known as the Captain of the Black Bulls.
And for some reason, he wore a hoppy coat.
There's a big festival going on today.
Festival?
I'll see you next time.
Tell me more about this big festival!
Well, I can tell you one thing, Osta.
It's pretty freaking awesome!
Does that help?
Yeah, totally!
Wait, I still don't understand!
That doesn't help at all.
You, tell us what this festival is and be as detailed as you can.
Me?
Oh, right, sure.
I'm your superior.
As you know, Magic Knight squads receive stars as a reward for good performance.
And we compete with all the usual suspects to see who can get the most.
This festival is where they announce the total number of stars distributed over the past year and crown the winning squad.
Oh!
Let's aim for the top!
Except our squad does nothing but cause trouble, which means we're always in a race for dead last.
No.
We're in last by a mile.
No one else has negative stars.
Really?
Come on, how terrible can we be?
As I was saying, the festival is attended and enjoyed by citizens all over the Clover Kingdom as the largest public event of its kind.
It's called...
The Star Festival.
Woo-hoo!
Nice one, Bot!
This is nuts!
I've never seen him get this fired up!
Yeah, festivals are fine, I guess.
It's, uh, you know, whatever.
Clothes say otherwise.
I'm with you, Captain Yummy!
Festival! Festival!
Oh, hey, wait a second!
Before we leave...
Huh?
If it's not a problem, do you think we could bring a couple friends along?
So cool!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Here we are.
Now you rascals go have some fun.
We still got plenty of free time before the announcement.
Yahoo! Where's the booze?
Festival food!
I think I'll grab a bite to eat, too.
I'll try to pick out a nice souvenir for my sweet sister.
I wonder if there's anybody here who wants to fight me!
Hey! Where were they selling you that funny-looking mask, mister?
It's my face.
Hey!
Whoa! Check it out!
There's so much stuff to do here!
I wish my friends in the village could see it!
Just try not to get distracted and wind up lost somewhere.
Then again, I guess I could walk around with you if you really wanted me to.
Hey!
Great! They made it!
Kahuno! In Kyoto!
It's been so long!
Hey, Asta! Looking good, man!
You too!
How did you get here?
I asked Finral to make a pit stop and pick him up for me!
Just wanted to do something nice for my adorable pal here.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have some girls to sweep off their feet.
My work's never done!
So this is a festival on land, huh? It's amazing!
You saved the underwater temple from the eye of the midnight sun.
And as if that wasn't enough, you bring us here too?
We're really grateful, Asta.
And my gorgeous goddess!
Wow! Look at all the shoves here!
Hey, careful! Don't strain yourself, Kahuno!
I'm sure she must be dying to sing.
Poor girl.
Kioto! You brought your foot, right?
Huh?
Yeah.
I preserved it with water magic, but why did you want me to bring it?
You'll see.
Here we go!
It's as good as new!
That's awesome!
It's from the Forest of Witches!
All I had to do was bottle some of the Queen's recovery magic!
Oh, wow! Incredible!
Look! I can dance again!
I'm just as good as I was before!
Am I still?
My voice! It's back!
So wait!
Does this mean…
Yes!
I can talk!
Noelle!
Thank you!
It's amazing!
How wonderful!
You can sing again!
I'm so grateful!
You're a real friend!
This is the best!
Yeah, anytime!
You are a real友ουν!!
It's a long meeting,
for the third time!
What about the BSL?
Anything to theüttu?
Yes!
There we go.
It's One Day...
I've been to you!
Look, there's so much...
Now everyone can hear me song again!
I've been to you..
You can sing again,
I
Beautiful singing!
Now we can achieve our dream of becoming pop stars!
Yeah! We're gonna make it big and filthy rich!
That's their first thought?
Priorities, I guess.
You're always thinking about the practical stuff.
Money's crucial! Anyway, this Star Festival only comes once a year, right?
So let's make the most of it!
Okay! Watch out, my goddess. I'm going to win your heart today.
Hey! There you are!
Perfect timing!
Oh, Magna, you surprised me. What's that huge thing you're holding?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
It's a fireworks cannon.
Did you say fireworks?
That's right. As soon as it gets good and dark out, we're gonna light up the whole sky with those things.
Sweet!
Oh, but wait, I was just about to head off to check out the sights with these three.
So ditch them. I outrank you.
Hold on. There's two guys and two girls here I understand now.
Looks like I just walked right in the middle of a double date, huh?
What?!
Man, you got moves, don't you, Shorty?
I guess?
What the heck is a double date anyway?
Oh, it's when two couples go out.
That isn't even close to what we're doing! How can you be such an idiot, Magna?
A date with my goddess? Sounds okay to me.
Poor thing. Still can't express her true feelings. Maybe I can help.
Come on, you guys! The four of us are finally together again, so let's have some fun!
You know what? I think we should make it into a double date!
Uh-oh! What did I get myself into?
Okay, it's time to get started!
So now it is a double date? That's way too forward for me!
Kahono seems really into this, though. Does that mean she likes Asta?
Kahono's trying to pair me up with my beautiful goddess.
You're the best, sis! I won't let you down! I still don't know what this is!
Oh, hey there!
Stick with me, Asta! This is gonna be a total blast!
Uh, okay! I guess I'll give it a try!
I see what she's up to! Getting all close to him like that!
Shall we dance our way along?
That's more like it!
Better make a move, Noel, or he's gonna spend the entire festival next to me!
You're about to learn that you've gotta fight for what you want!
Oh, yummy!
Mm-hmm!
Could I trouble you to write a special message in mayonnaise for me?
Sure, what would you like?
Love goddess! For the young lady here!
I can't get it to shoot!
You're actually supposed to use your magic, sir!
Here!
I'll use mine!
Oh, takes a lot!
Sam, please don't aim that outside the booth!
Look! I found a mask fit for a goddess!
Whoa! We really showed that gun game who's boss!
We sure did! You're so good at that stuff!
I even got these little ball things as a consolation prize!
Those two kind of look good together!
Wait, why do I care about something ridiculous like that anyway?
Behold, my goddess! I bought crepes!
Ugh! What's it gonna take to get Noel to fight for her man?
At this point, I'm just getting in the way of their relationship!
That's it! It's time to change tactics! And I've got a secret weapon!
What is this place?
It's haunted house, idiot!
What's that?
Really? Wow, you don't know anything at all, do you?
We didn't have festivals back where I come from!
All the scary stuff in here is the perfect excuse for couples to cozy up!
That's why they call it the Couples Factory!
But we'll need to bring out the big gums if we want it to stick!
Uh, Kahuno, don't leave me, okay? I don't want my goddess to see me all scared!
Do your stuff, ghosts! Or should I say angels of love?
What's that?
Really? Wow, you don't know anything at all, do you?
We didn't have festivals back where I come from!
All the scary stuff in here is the perfect excuse for couples to cozy up!
That's why they call it the Couples Factory!
But we'll need to bring out the big gums if we want it to stick!
Uh, Kahuno? Don't leave me, okay? I don't want my goddess to see me all scared!
Stuff ghosts, or should I say angels of love?
Ha-ha! All right, gentlemen, here's the plan!
You two scare the pants off the customers!
And that's when I step in!
Don't be frightened by those phantoms, m'lady!
Oh my, you're so wonderful!
Indeed, I am, you smart girl!
I'm also the most powerful of all the magic knights!
And just between us, I'm the next captain of the green praying mantises!
Even so, without you, I'm just alone!
Ha-ha!
Let us enjoy the evening together!
Oh, yes!
And that's how I'll get myself a girlfriend!
There's nothing to it!
Easy for you to say!
Yes, it's showtime!
Don't let me down, you two!
When are we supposed to see the ghosts?
Why are you asking me?
Boo!
That's it! Now they're good and terrified!
I bet those two are holding on to each other for dear life right about now!
Or not!
Leave us alone, you freaky little freaks!
Get lost! I won't let you attack the capital again!
What?!
Where did those two go?
Leave me!
Oh, let go of my legs!
Hey, stop! Look closer!
It's just me!
I get it!
You're the ringleader!
Ah!
Really?
You're saying they were just fakes?
Of course they were!
I can't believe you got us all kicked out!
Come on, you were just as scared as I was!
I was not scared!
Me either!
Rats!
Foiled again!
Noelle is enough of a problem, but Asta's so oblivious!
I wonder how he feels about her!
Hey Asta!
I've been meaning to ask you, what do you think about Noelle?
W-what do I think?
Uh...
Well, I, uh...
Where's my mommy?
Is she lost?
Let her mom go!
Hey, are you okay?
She's so shabby!
I guess they're commoners!
They probably came here looking for work!
She's so loud!
Where are her manners?
How dare these filthy commoners ruin the Star Festival for everyone else!
Only those with powerful magic can live in the upper realms.
They look down upon those who have less magic power,
despite the fact that all of us are human.
Oh...
Should we...
What's the matter?
Is there something we can do to help you?
Listen, I can't understand you if you're crying.
Try to calm down.
Here there, it's not that bad.
Hey, I know!
Little girl!
Look what I can do!
Here!
See?
It's pretty neat, right?
This is perfect!
Asta the Superman
Yes, he can do anything!
He may be tiny, but he's super loud!
So what if he's the dummy?
He's got the strongest body!
Sure!
He may be worthless when it comes to magic,
but he'll slash through any spell!
That's not a compliment!
No, he can't use magic, but he's still pretty swell!
Asta, Asta, Asta!
Superman!
Asta the Superman!
Yes, he can do anything!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
He's got the strongest body!
La la la la la la la la!
Worthy's doing magic, but slash, he's any spell!
La la la la la!
La la la la la la la, la, la la la!
Oh yeah, he's pretty swell!
Asta! Asta! Asta!
Asta!
Superman!
Oh, wow!
Please watch, my goddess. This dance is dedicated to you!
Okay, can you please tell me your name?
Emma.
Kahono, do you think you could use your song magic to send this little girl's name to her mother wherever she is?
Hey, good idea! Just leave it to me!
Emma!
Oh, how can I ever thank you?
Look at that! You're back together!
Thank you for helping me find my mom.
Mommy's here so she can find work, remember? I thought I told you not to wander off all by yourself.
I'm sorry, but the festival just looked like so much fun.
I really can't express my gratitude.
That emblem! You're a member of House Silva?
Silva? Oh, a thousand pardons. I do hope my daughter didn't do anything to offend you.
What? Royalty? Look at her hair. She's a Silva.
A commoner like that shouldn't even be speaking to her.
You're right. I am royalty.
We're said to have the greatest magic power in the kingdom.
Which is why we must use it to help others.
Fainly putting yourself above everyone else and looking down on the people around you,
that's something you only do if your heart is small.
Emma can enjoy the star festival too.
Whether someone is royalty or a commoner doesn't matter.
We can all have fun together!
You're amazing! Thank you!
I've been meaning to ask you, what do you think about Noel?
If I had to say...
Hmm?
You're pretty great. I like you a lot, Noel.
Right out of the park!
Huh? Now what's wrong?
Bingo!
Come on, Noel. This is your chance. Just say it already!
Where did that come from?
I swear you get dumber every day!
What did I do?
Go, heart!
Oh, he'll live, right?
She is royalty.
That's gonna hurt tomorrow.
Great.
Asta!
Did you let her send you flying just for me?
Sheesh.
With her stubbornness and his foolishness, they'll never couple up.
But I said something nice.
She's okay.
I always knew that we'd end up settling the score eventually.
Sheesh.
What the?
Hey, what's going on?
Hey!
奇跡を描こう
凍らしあとは 五千歩の上踊る
Just a melody
僕らの誓いはここにある
口ずさむ合言葉は
I'll make it true
My song, my days
この世界に響かせゆこう
駆け抜けたい日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らならあきらめない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
曲がりくなった道 さあ僕らには
輝ける明日を映す
曲がりくなった道具
Clover Clips
The Hitman
My angel
I mean, my client, Marie
Your big brother's about to finish him off
Just like you wanted
The target is that dog
Marie really fancies these lately
So I plan to use all of my magic power to take it down
Mirror magic
Go real double
After that
Comes the flight refrain
What? I can't hit it!
Oh yeah, I forgot
Some short guy with giant muscles was using that gun earlier
And must have busted it
He's dead
Listen, Asta, I let you take me on that, uh, date or whatever
So you better show me some gratitude
After all, I am royalty
Black Clover, page 68
Battle to the death
Yami versus Jack
Huh? What's the captain up to?
?
That's a great deal
I'll see you guys
Bye
So I'll see you guys